A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Yay! Yay! Yay!
It's done, Lord Death. We have officially accomplished our mission.
Well done, Maka. You have successfully collected 99 Kishun souls and the soul of one witch. Congratulations. As promised, I will make Soul my personal weapon.
You'll finally be at Dead Scythe.
Yeah!
Hey, what are you doing down there on the floor? You're gonna be late for school.
Hmm.
can you hear me?
Six audits are even better to meme...
Thank you for speaking air...
I'll see you next time.
We'll see.
Yeah. Last year, I would have had the highest score if it wasn't for Ox.
There are a couple of hard workers in this class who could beat out my score.
Like her. Last year, Maka came in second.
Right behind me.
Yo, Blackstar, do you know why they call this test a super written exam?
Huh?
It's because supposedly whoever comes in first is destined to make a death site.
What? Seriously?
Seriously? That's right. It's my destiny.
Mama was at the top of her year, too. I have to come in first. It's in my blood.
It's settled. I'm going to get first and turn you into a death site, Tsubaki.
Okay.
Wait, cool. This is our first written exam ever. Let's go.
Just because they put the word super in front of it doesn't mean I'm going to study.
You sound pretty confident. You aren't going to prepare for it at all.
I am a reaper. I've got a pretty good grasp of cosmology.
I forgot. I'll have to compete against Kid this year, too. This could get real ugly.
What on earth are you doing, spirit?
I'm sending positive energy to Maka so she'll do well on the test.
Okay.
Anything else?
No. Continue.
The Super Written Exam.
Heart-pounding, reeling, and restless? You're kidding.
Okay. It's time to study.
Hey, so Maka, are tests like this a lot of fun to take?
Uh-huh. You get to find out how much you've learned so far.
You can tell from your score and class ranking.
It's kind of like a game, almost.
But I have to study extra hard this time.
They say that whoever gets the top score will create a death scythe.
From what I hear, it's really difficult to become a death scythe.
Your papa must be amazing, Maka.
It's my mom who's amazing.
She managed to make my good-for-nothing papa into a death scythe.
Okay. So the study of phasmology began with who again?
Oh, you're studying for the Super Written Test thingy too, Sol?
Yeah. I'm a little busy here.
Leave me alone.
Oh, that's no fun!
I'm bored! Play with me!
Oh, killer!
Four hundred and ninety-eight?
Four hundred and ninety-nine?
Five...
...hundred!
The next time I get one wrong, it's going to be a thousand sit-ups.
Okay, let's see.
What's this say?
Okay.
Dammit!
Let's quit with the penalty exercises.
You're just three.
I'll help you.
Five!
Smart girl transformation complete.
Let's study.
You look so smart, see?
Yeah!
Oh, my.
So you two were serious about hitting the books, huh?
If you guys need help with anything, um, that doesn't look like studying.
It's break time right now.
I've got this one hair that's longer than the others.
I can't concentrate because it's bothering me.
Idiot!
What do you think you're doing?
Eyebrow grooming is to be left up to me!
What happens if the left and right sides are uneven?
Kid, do you remember how long it took the last time I let you pluck them for me?
It was a month.
Fine then.
I promise to do it quicker this time.
Please, I beg you.
Huh?
If you're going to keep begging me...
Yes!
First, we need a blueprint.
Go somewhere else.
We're trying to study.
What concept should I go for?
Strong and yet subtle, maybe?
Yes, that's perfect.
You need to get over it, kid.
They're just eyebrows.
Marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka.
Marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka, marka.
Oh, my God.
Why won't anybody play with me?
That test must be a really big deal.
A relaxing bath.
Just what I needed.
I'm so proud of Blackstar for studying this hard.
I never thought I'd see the day.
I'll make some dinner to reward him.
I'll make some dinner.
Yahoo!
Crap, that was loud.
I have to be quiet.
Very quiet.
No more studying for me.
That stuff's way too boring.
I'll just steal the test.
Like any good assassin would do.
There they are.
With this, there's no way I'll fail.
Mine will be the biggest score in the whole class.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Blackstar?
Where are you?
How's the studying going?
I told you.
We're on a break.
You've been on break for three days now!
My nails weren't painted.
It was bothering me.
All done.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha.
I'm finished.
I've done all that I can tonight.
Now it's time to rest up for tomorrow.
My little girl will get first place tomorrow.
She will, she will, she will, she will.
Maka, maka, maka.
She will, she will, she will.
Maka will get first place tomorrow.
Maka, maka, maka.
Woo!
I will do my best tomorrow.
I'm ready!
I'll be proctoring your exam today.
Just one more thing before we get started.
Yeah, uh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh.
Ah!
It's Blackstar!
A certain idiot decided to sneak into Professor Stein's laboratory last night to steal the exam.
Yeah.
Ooh?
So, don't be an idiot like this guy.
You'll have 60 minutes.
Keep your eyes on your own paper.
Start writing!
You're fine.
Just relax.
Anyone who spends all that time studying to do this honestly is a chump.
I prefer to work smart instead of hard.
That's why I look for shortcuts.
The highest score on this test wins no matter what.
So, who cares how you get it?
My entire body is covered in cheat sheets.
How's this for a shortcut, Maka?
I'm going to ace this thing no problem.
You sure this is everything you have?
Why?
You want to take my underwear too?
What an idiot.
Go back to your seat.
But this is the only other chance you're going to get.
Yeah, yeah.
No, you need to concentrate on my test.
Looks like the next viewer fill in the blank.
Let's see.
Complete the following sentences as accurately as you can.
One.
A sound soul...
Easy.
Dwells within a sound...
Okay.
A sound soul dwells within sound skin and sound cuticles.
That doesn't sound right.
I hadn't even answered a single question yet.
This is the opposite of cool.
Wait.
Maybe I'm not done for.
The brilliant kid is sitting right next to me.
It's not near enough.
The freak's still writing his name.
He's useless.
And here?
She's writing with a crayon.
She's worn down the illa quite a lot.
Oh!
Giraffe!
I love giraffes.
Of course.
A giraffe.
Answer this question true or false.
Uh-huh.
It's just like Professor Stein to throw in a trick question to trip us up.
Is this a trick?
Hmm.
Now it couldn't be.
Professor Stein wouldn't do anything to trick his students.
False.
You can't fool me with that little trick, Professor.
Excuse me, Sid.
I'm all finished.
Just read a book or something.
Know-it-all brat.
Ten minutes remaining.
What?
I'm running out of time.
And Kid's still trying to write his name.
All done.
What?
Woo-hoo!
So pretty!
You made her test into a giraffe.
Better watch out.
I can break your neck.
That's pretty good.
Damn.
It's awful.
It's just awful.
Awful.
No matter what I do, I can't get the K right.
I've been useless garbage.
I'm a horrible, disgusting person who doesn't deserve to live another day.
Uh, Sid.
Kid just collapsed.
Let him be.
Sol.
Black Star.
You're writing in blood?
That's right.
You saw the answers in the laboratory.
And now you're trying to give them to me.
I'll carry out your dying wish.
I promise I will.
What good is your stupid autograph?
You choose.
Be quiet or die.
Test is almost over.
All right.
I've checked everything.
It looks good.
You have ten seconds.
Yes.
Five seconds left.
It's all perfect.
Test is over.
It's been over since I got strip searched.
Man, am I worn out.
I know.
That was a tough one, huh?
Yeah.
I think it was too hard.
I second that.
Amen.
Cheers.
Come on, you've got to be kidding me with this, Maka.
The test is all over, and you're still studying?
No, no.
I made a mess while I was studying earlier,
and when I was cleaning up, I found this old photo album.
Huh.
Is that you with your creepy dad?
He's so young.
Uh-huh.
Papa was only 18 years old when I was born.
He used to read a lot of books to me back then.
Huh.
You think your old man's the reason you love to read books so much now?
Maybe he is.
Yay!
Congratulations, Papa.
The results of the super test thingy have been posted.
That's something a man can drink to.
I think it's great that you spent three days straight sending out positive energy for Maka.
Maka sure is amazing, huh?
At the very top of her class, just like my wife was.
You mean your ex-wife?
Yeah, my ex.
Listen, Blair, can I ask you a favor?
Mia.
I wanted to get Maka a present to congratulate her on the test.
Could you casually find out what her favorite book is and buy it for?
Here, here's some money for the book and a letter from me to Maka.
Shouldn't you give it to her yourself, Papa?
No.
If I tried to give it to her directly, there's a good chance she wouldn't accept it.
Why are you laughing?
It's nothing.
I can just tell that you really love Maka.
If it's a book you want, then consider it done.
Thank you, Blair.
Oh, no.
I went and spent the money on myself instead.
I couldn't resist the temptation.
I'm used to being the one who's doing the tempting.
Now I'm nothing but a dirty cat burglar.
All I have to do is shrink it a little and it'll be perfect.
Pump, pump, pumpkin, pump, pumpkin.
Now drop the card inside and done.
I'm home, Maka.
Hey, welcome back.
There's pumpkin pie if you're hungry.
Sounds good.
Here, Maka, I have a present for you from your Papa.
It's to celebrate your good test score.
What could it be?
Ta-da!
What could that creep possibly be thinking
sending sexy underwear to his own daughter?
Hold on, Maka.
Um, I think there's a card in here
that's supposed to go with it.
Oh, great.
Congratulations.
I know you worked hard to get such a high score.
That's why I'm sending you this present.
I hope you can use it to relax and have a little fun.
You've earned it from Maka.
What kind of fun does he mean?
Just what kind of girl does he think I am?
I'll bet Maka's enjoying her present right now.
He's so creepy.
I hate him.
Maka.
O-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o-o
Thank you.
Scaredy-cat whizzen or marry friends?
Watch it or I'll take your soul.